velocitymicro.com 2018-12-15

# Our Commitment To Online Privacy - Privacy Policy | Velocity Micro

Velocity Micro has drafted this document, which details how we gather and disseminate information, in an effort to demonstrate our strong commitment to online privacy. Please contact us if you have any questions about our privacy policy. 

### Use and Security of Order Information

All information requested when you place an order is secured by Secure Sockets Layer (SSL) technology to protect the loss, misuse, or alteration of information placed under our control. Note that on the checkout page, the Address bar in your web browser begins with an "https" instead of the regular "http". A small yellow lock symbol appears in the lower right-hand corner of your browser. 

When you place an order, VelocityMicro.com requests information such as contact information, shipping information, Internet Protocol (IP) address, credit card number, and demographic information. 

  * Your contact information is used for the sole purpose of contacting you regarding your order or other services (e.g., technical support). 
  * Your shipping information is used for the sole purpose of shipping your order.
  * Your financial information is used for the sole purpose of billing you for products.
  * Your IP address is recorded for several purposes: to help diagnose problems with our server, to administer our Web site, to help identify you and your shopping cart, to protect you against fraudulent transactions, and to gather broad demographic information. 
  * Your demographic information is used to help us tailor our products and services to your needs.

### We do not sell, rent, trade, or otherwise market your information (demographic, contact, financial, or otherwise) with ANY third party.

Your information remains solely in our possession. 

### Use of Information Collected in Contests

When you register for a contest on VelocityMicro.com, we require you to submit contact information such as name, email address, phone number, address, etc. We use this information for purposes of informing the winner, shipping the prize, and also for collecting demographic information. 

### We do not sell, rent, trade, or otherwise market your contest with ANY third party.

Your information remains solely in our possession. 

### Use of Newsletter Information

When you register to receive the Velocity Micro newsletter, we require you to submit your email address. We use this address for the sole purpose of sending you the requested newsletter. You may opt out of the newsletter at any time by sending an email to [vmnews@velocitymicro.com](mailto:vmnews@velocitymicro.com) with "Remove" in the subject line. 

### We do not sell, rent, trade, or otherwise market your newsletter with ANY third party.

Your information remains solely in our possession. 

### Children's Guidelines

We do not collect or use any online contact information or identifiable off-line contact information about a child without parental consent. We do not distribute personally identifiable information about children without parental consent. We do not give children the ability to post or distribute personal information without prior consent. We do not entice children with games or contests that would encourage them to disclose personal information. 

### Opt Out/Opt In

VelocityMicro.com allows users to opt in to receive an email newsletter from us. Users may unsubscribe at any time by sending an email message to [vmnews@velocitymicro.com](mailto:vmnews@velocitymicro.com) with the word "Remove" in the subject line. 

### Disclaimer

This site contains links to other sites. VelocityMicro.com is not responsible for the content or privacy practices of these sites. 

### Contact Us

If you have any additional questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact us:  

  * Velocity Micro
  * 500 Southlake Blvd.
  * Richmond, VA 23236
  * (804) 419-0900
